indiangiftsportal.com 2005-12-12

# Indian Gifts Portal

_**Indian Gifts Portal** is committed to safeguarding your privacy online_. We recognize your need for reasonable control of personally identifiable information that you share with Indian Gifts Portal. 

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order. This will used only for the service you have sought and would not be under any circumstances passed on fo any other commercial purpose. Indian Gifts Portal will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Although we track the total number of visitors to each of sites in an aggregate form to allow us to update an improve our sites, personally identifiable informatio is not extracted in this process. Any cookie technology (where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor's computer) will only be used to track non-personal information such as type of browser,operating system, and domain names to improve our visitor's online experience. 

**How does Indian Gifts Portal protect customer information?**

When you place orders it is through a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input including your credit card number, before it is sent to us. This makes it unreadable as it travels across the Internet. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

**Will Indian Gifts Portal disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

**Indian Gifts Portal** does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Indian Gifts Portal. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**IMPORTANT: Kindly also refer [_IndiaMART Privacy Policy_](http://www.indiamart.com/privacy-policy.html)**
